Hello friends, today in this video we will learn how to get
accident insurance done with the help of phone, right?
You
people must be knowing
what accident insurance is, more about health
insurance, most people know about general life
insurance and health insurance plan,
but
their knowledge about personal accident insurance remains
limited, so today
in this video we will learn how to get accident insurance done with the help of phone, whether it is
someone's, but in this video today we will tell you
how it is done,
you simply have to click here,
click on insurance,
after clicking on insurance you will see
bike car, domestic travel, international
travel, term life accident, so what you simply have to do is you have to click on
accident, you can
see more information as you
will scroll down and you will also see it, like
here help, 90
etc. you simply have to click on accident,
okay, after clicking there
you will see, select SAM insurance like
39, you will have to pay in that, in case of an
accident you will get ₹1 lakh  You will get it,
right? And yes, if you take insurance in the name of a person in the morning,
that person will get
Rs. 10 lakhs by doing this,
so what you have to do is simply click on 39,
for example
[music]
we have chosen insurance, right, you
can also see its benefits, you will
give your email ID or your mobile number, whatever
you do,
okay,
date of birth, here you will be told some terms and
conditions, so you have to click on it
or simply you will get Pay,
as soon as you click on Pay,
you will see that your UPI ID will be generated, you will
enter whatever number is there and the money will be
deducted from your
account, so friend, do tell me how you liked the video
by commenting,
thank you.